marcatoapp.com 2013-12-27

# Marcato Digital Solutions

### Marcato's Commitment to Privacy

Marcato has created a privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to data privacy and protection. This policy sets forth our information gathering and utilization practices for this web site. Our Privacy Policy is compliant with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Document Act (PIPEDA), which applies generally to personal information in relation to commercial transactions. To learn more about PIPEDA, please refer to the following web site: <http://www.privcom.gc.ca/index_e.asp>

### What We Collect and Where

From the web site we collect the following information:  
Unique identifiers  
Contact information  
Financial information  
Marcato does not intentionally gather personal data about visitors who are under the age of 13.  
Marcato does not view the files that you upload, download or store using our product, and does not monitor or disclose any information regarding your specific files and data without your permission, unless required by law applicable to Marcato, or in accordance with this policy and our terms of service.

### IP Address and Cookies

An Internet Protocol (IP) address can be used to help diagnose problems with a server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to a site, and administer and improve the site.  
We use cookies to collect non-personal information that enables us to better understand and improve the usability, performance and effectiveness of our product. Cookies are unique text files sent to your browser and stored on your computer. Disabling the use of cookies may affect your ability to use some features of our product.  
Marcato also collects general information about visits to our website. This information includes parameters such as the number of visits and browser details. No personal details are present in this data and it is utilized for the sole purpose of better understanding website usage to improve user experiences.

### Contact Information/Financial Information

We will ask you for personal information when you sign up for any specific benefit or purpose that requires registration. Personal information that we collect may vary with each registration and may include one or more of the following categories: name, physical address, an e-mail address, and phone number. Financial information collected such as credit card information including credit card number and expiration date, and billing address is stored and only used to bill the user for products/services. This information will not be used in a manner different than the purpose for which it was originally collected, unless Marcato has first obtained your consent to do so.  
You may, at any time, choose to correct or update the information that you have submitted to Marcato by updating your account on our website. 

### Using/Sharing Your Information

All information collected by Marcato is used for purposes of facilitating our services, providing support to users, improving our services, and administration. We will not share, sell, or rent your personal information to others. The following are exceptions to this general policy:  
i.) Affiliates and Service Providers - third parties who need access to Marcato user information for the purpose of hosting our servers or archiving personal information for us are required by Marcato to maintain high level of security.  
ii.) Legal Process/Enforcement - Marcato may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to enforce the applicable Terms and Conditions or in conjunction with an investigation or legal action or proceeding.  
iii.) Marcato may transfer part or all of your information in the case of a merger, acquisition, or bankruptcy.

### Onward Transfer of Personal Information Outside Your Country of Residence

Any personal information that we may collect on this site, will be stored and processed on our servers located only in the United States and by using this site, you consent to the transfer.

### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or method of data storage can be guaranteed 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to protect your personal information by following industry standards, we cannot ensure or warrant the absolute security of any information you transmit to us or archive at this site.

### Opt-out Choice

You may receive periodic messages from us with information specific to the site and required for the normal functioning of the site as well as for new products or services or upcoming events. If you would prefer not to receive periodic email messages, you may opt-out by following the instructions in the email.

### Links to Third Party Sites

This site may contain links to other websites with whom we have a business relationship. These links may include online advertisements that we deem to be appropriate. Any information that you provide in the process of registration or purchase will not be transferred to these sites. These websites have their own policies regarding privacy, and you should review those policies prior to using the websites. Marcato has no responsibility for linked websites and these links are provided solely for the convenience and information of users.

### Privacy questions

If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact the owner and operator of this website business at:  
Marcato Digital Solutions, Inc.  
Attn: Darren Gallop  
P.O. Box 852, Station A  
Sydney, NS Canada B1P 6J1  
Email: [darren@maracatodigital.com](mailto:darren@maracatodigital.com)  
Tel: (902) 539-9517  
Toll Free: (888) 246-1373  
Facsimile: (866) 895-1976
